And I'd like to know why no one in the
media is talking about the investigation
or the fact that there should have been
an investigation into whether or not
Jeffrey Epstein was working for a
foreign intelligence service. You know,
let's
So, so that's really interesting. So,
look, you you've studied into this. What
is the evidence that he might have been?
He is the a textbook example of an of an
access agent. You're, like I said the
last time I was on the show, Piers,
you're not going to recruit Bill
Clinton. You're not going to recruit
Bill Gates. You're not going to recruit
Alan Dersowitz. But you can recruit
someone who gets close to those people.
You can give them something that you can
hold over their heads if you have to in
the end and then you report back to your
handlers everything that they